rapmusic.com 2007-06-10

# Rapmusic.com - Rap / Hip hop music and culture. Your total source for Rap/Hip-hop Entertainment and Information Online.

800media.com and its advertisers and affiliates are deeply committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. Below is information outlining our continued support for the responsible management of consumer information. 

**Collection of Personal Information**  
800media.com maintains the confidentiality, security and integrity of personal information that we obtain from our users. However, unless otherwise specified, we may share email addresses and sell or share all other information with our affiliates and with carefully selected companies who we think can offer you services and products of interest to you. If you do not wish to have your information shared, write to us at [Jeff@800media.com](mailto:Jeff@800media.com%20). 800media.com will periodically e-mail special offers pertaining to sites within the 800Media network. Users may opt-out of receiving these mailings; see the Stop Receiving Mail section below. Our site may use order forms and registration forms for users to request information, products, and services. We may collect contact information (like users' email addresses, names, telephone numbers and mailing addresses) and financial information (like account or credit card numbers) through these forms. Contact information from the forms is used to send orders to our customers, to send information about our products and services and for the purposes of record keeping. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the Stop Receiving Mail section below. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services. Our online surveys and contests sometimes ask users for contact information (like their email addresses) or information about hobbies or interests. We sometimes use this information to send news about our products and services and to help us provide our customers with better service. Users may opt-out of receiving these mailings; see the Stop Receiving Mail section below. We sometimes contact by telephone users who have ordered products or services from us with information regarding their order. 

**About IP Addresses**  
800media.com collects IP addresses for the purposes of system administration and to report anonymous aggregate information to third parties. An IP address is a number that's automatically assigned to your computer whenever you're surfing the Web. Web servers -- the big computers that "serve" up Web pages -- automatically identify your computer by its IP address. When guests request pages from 800media.com, our servers log the users' IP addresses. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means that a user's session will be logged, but the user remains anonymous to us. 

**Use of Cookies**  
Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. The use of cookies is an industry standard, you'll find them at most major Web sites. 800media.com sometimes uses cookies to track certain information for our users' convenience and to understand our customers better. 

**Consumer Information**  
During the process of delivering an ad to you, 800media.com does not collect any personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address. However, 800media.com does obtain some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet Service Provider you use to connect to the Internet, your browser type, or the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh or Windows, for example). The information collected by 800media.com is used for the purpose of targeting ads and measuring ad effectiveness on behalf of our advertisers.

**Links to Other Sites**  
You should be aware that when you are on 800media.com you could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. There are links to other sites from our site that take you outside our service. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, or otherwise collect data or solicit personal information. Always be aware of where you end up on the Web. 

**Security**  
The importance of security for all personally identifiable information associated with our users is of utmost concern to us. We exercise great care in providing secure transmission of our users' financial information from their computers to our servers, utilizing encryption software. Only those employees who need access to our users' information in order to do their jobs are allowed access. Any employee who violates our privacy and/or security policies is subject to disciplinary action, including possible termination and civil and/or criminal prosecution. 

**How to Stop Receiving Mail from Us**  
email: [Jeff@800media.com ](mailto:Jeff@800media.com%20)

**Your Acceptance of These Terms**  
By using this site, you signify your assent to the 800media.com Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our site. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. You can send e-mail to us with any further questions.

**Contacting Us**  
If you have any questions on our privacy policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, you can contact: [Jeff@800media.com ](mailto:Jeff@800media.com%20)

Copyright © 1998-2005 800Media, Inc. All Rights Reserved.  
No portions of this site may be duplicated without permission from 800Media, Inc.
